{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262793676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262793675"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262803324","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262803324"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262803944","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262803944"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262804723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262804723"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262805883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262805882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262806329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262806329"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262807103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262807103"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262809476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262809476"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262810299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262810299"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262811132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262811132"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262811765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262811765"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262811988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262811988"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262812712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262812711"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOA"," userResponse":" MADOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262813555","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262813555"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262813748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262813748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262814585","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262814584"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" MEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262814723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262814723"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262814796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262814796"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" MEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262822668","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262822667"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262829474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262829473"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 47c036ce-28d9-4067-a265-7113b636aab1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262843872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262843872"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-5-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262849138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262849138"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-0-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262857491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262857491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-7-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262862690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262862690"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262870815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262870814"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262875650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262875650"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262883802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262883802"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-1-0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262889708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262889708"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-5-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262911910","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262911909"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-5-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262919975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262919975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 285f324a-d03b-46ee-8f1a-dfc4ee26a5fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-5-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262930656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262930656"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262931040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262931040"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262931692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262931692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262931893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262931893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262932795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262932794"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262935081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262935081"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262936134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262936134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262938781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262938781"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262939855","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262939854"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262940568","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262940568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262943356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262943356"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262944341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262944340"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" INARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262945043","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262945041"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262945805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262945805"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262947996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262947995"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262948776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262948776"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262949280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262949280"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262953964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262953964"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262954752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262954751"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262955876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262955875"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262958831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262958830"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262959674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262959674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262959887","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262959887"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262960251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262960250"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262960402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262960401"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262961034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262961033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262964062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262964061"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262964984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262964983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262965888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262965888"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262966521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262966521"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262966604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262966603"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262967157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262967157"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262970481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262970480"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262971359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262971358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" STESHENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262971803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262971803"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262972459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262972458"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262973034","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262973034"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262975687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262975686"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262976530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262976530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262979397","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262979397"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262980593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262980592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262981385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262981385"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262984588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262984586"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262985028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262985027"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262985420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262985419"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262985858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262985858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262986309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262986309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262987025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262987024"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262990263","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262990262"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262991355","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262991355"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262991751","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262991750"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262992707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262992707"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262995975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262995974"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262996827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262996827"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262997781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262997781"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262998705","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262998705"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262998809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262998809"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549262999537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549262999537"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263000222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263000222"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263000950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263000950"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263003704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263003704"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263005058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263005058"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263005867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263005867"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263007077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263007076"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263010250","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263010249"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263010794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263010793"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263011123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263011122"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263012088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263012087"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263012867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263012867"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263013472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263013471"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263016293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263016292"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263017017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263017017"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263017759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263017759"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263017982","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263017981"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263018731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263018731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263021823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263021823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263022187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263022186"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263022910","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263022910"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263023498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263023497"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263024089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263024088"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263026959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263026959"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263029565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263029564"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263031031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263031031"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263034427","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263034426"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263035099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263035099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263036186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263036185"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263039022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263039020"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263039135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263039134"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263047215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263047214"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" c2e6685f-ae92-4074-9008-9ea915658c3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263061068","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263061068"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263068546","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263068546"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263077070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263077070"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_1-5-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263083604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263083604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263091437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263091437"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_5-7-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263112773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263112773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263119065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263119064"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-6-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263125256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263125256"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-1-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263131294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263131293"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-1-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263136177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263136176"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-1-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263141787","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263141786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263147193","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263147192"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263154883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263154883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-8-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263161485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263161484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 31f62642-0455-423a-a93b-9040408395d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-8-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263170185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263170185"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 8873a848-3dfb-4efc-a212-11786ec56a2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_O-U-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263174437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263174437"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 8873a848-3dfb-4efc-a212-11786ec56a2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_I-U-E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263179204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263179204"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 8873a848-3dfb-4efc-a212-11786ec56a2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_E-A-U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263184625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263184625"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 8873a848-3dfb-4efc-a212-11786ec56a2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_E-A-U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263185745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263185744"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 8873a848-3dfb-4efc-a212-11786ec56a2c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_U_E-A-U"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263195849","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263195847"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263196092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263196091"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263196536","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263196536"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263196746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263196745"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263197489","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263197489"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263200548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263200548"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263201410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263201410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263201936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263201935"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263202680","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263202680"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263203019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263203018"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263206188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263206187"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263207363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263207363"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263207837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263207837"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263208081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263208081"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263208828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263208828"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263209247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263209247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263212284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263212283"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263212915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263212914"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263213737","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263213737"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263214574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263214573"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263217616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263217616"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263218649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263218647"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263219251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263219251"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263219802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263219801"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263222929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263222928"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263223788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263223788"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263224404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263224403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263225258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263225257"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263228224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263228224"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263229366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263229366"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263230467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263230467"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263233761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263233761"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263234604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263234603"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263235530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263235530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263236395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263236395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263239743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263239743"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263240056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263240055"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263240604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263240604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263243236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263243236"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263244259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263244258"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALALA"," userResponse":" ANALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263247399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263247399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263249058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263249058"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263249683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263249682"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263252718","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263252718"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263254007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263254007"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263256864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263256862"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263256961","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263256961"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" df5c223e-4013-43fb-9c2b-68bd2be77fcd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263277818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263277817"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263285296","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263285296"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263295492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263295491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263301706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263301706"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263309204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263309204"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263315802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263315802"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_A_E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263322500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263322499"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_E_U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263329183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263329183"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_O_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263335839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263335838"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_U_I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263342486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263342486"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_E_U"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263349158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263349158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_I"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263355810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263355810"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263363305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263363304"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263373534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263373533"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263382058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263382058"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2q.AV.mc.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263392848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263392848"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263401071","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263401070"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549263410521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549263410521"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190204_094617"," gameId":" 9f8cbe56-b6a4-4de4-bed5-a285288a75af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_U..U.vow.10.rand.say.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_O_U_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}